const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "who is the father of Computer ?",
        a : "John Simon",
        b : "Charles Babbage",
        c : "AdaLovlace",
        d : "no option",
        correct: "b"

    },

      {
        id: 2,
        question: "what is the full meaning of CPU ?",
        a : "Control Part Unit",
        b : "Computer Programming Unit",
        c : "Central Production Unit",
        d : "Central Processing Unit",
        correct: "d"

    }

    ,

      {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the full meaning of ECMA?",
        a : "Europian Computer Manufacturer Association",
        b : "Electronic Computer Manufacturer Association",
        c : "Electrical Computer Manual Assembly",
        d : "no option",
        correct: "a"

    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "what is the total internal angle in a pentagon ?",
      a : "360 deg",
      b : "480 deg",
      c : "540 deg",
      d : "720 deg",
      correct: "c"

  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "If it takes 3 men to complete a job in 120 mins, in how many hours will it take a man to complete the same job under same condtion ?",
    a : "6 hours",
    b : "18 hours",
    c : "8 hours",
    d : "14 hours",
    correct: "a"

},

{
  id: 6,
  question: "If Musa bought a car at a price of â‚¦5000000 in 2017, and made a profit percentage of 75% for selling it in 2025. How much did MUsa sold the car?",
  a : "8,750,000",
  b : "8,150,000",
  c : "8,450,000",
  d : "8,950,000",
  correct: "a"

},

{
  id: 7,
  question: "Ada read the stroy book diligently, what part of speech is 'diligently'?",
  a : "adverb",
  b : "adjective",
  c : "conjuction",
  d : "pronoun",
  correct: "a"

},

{
  id: 8,
  question: "Camsy didn't come to school?",
  a : "did she",
  b : "does she",
  c : "isn't it",
  d : "she did",
  correct: "a"

},

{
  id: 9,
  question: "Habeeb travelled to US --------- 2012?",
  a : "for",
  b : "since",
  c : "at",
  d : "no option",
  correct: "b"

},


{
  id: 10,
  question: "Who is the president of Nigeria?",
  a : "Bola Sanwolu",
  b : "Ahmed Sanwolu",
  c : "Ahmed Tinubu",
  d : "Peter Obi",
  correct: "c"

},

{
  id: 11,
  question: "Who is the governor of Lagos State?",
  a : "Sanwolu Babatunde",
  b : "Raji Fshola",
  c : "Ambode Thompson",
  d : "Sanwolu Babajide",
  correct: "d"

},

{
  id: 12,
  question: "who is the CEO of codeprof academy?",
  a : "Nelson Mandela",
  b : "Wale Adenuga",
  c : "Aliko Dangote",
  d : "Prof Thompson Musiliu ",
  correct: "d"

}

]

